<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>erg home</title>
    <link>https://ergreports.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on erg home</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 13 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://ergreports.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://ergreports.com/workforce-engagement/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ergreports.com/workforce-engagement/</guid>
      <description>Creating an engaged workforce 💖We apply behavioral principles and methods to answer questions of employee sentiment within the broader organizational system. An important component of this systemic change process includes our engagement survey developed in partnership with Eagle I.O.
Engagement survey 💃The engagement survey responses are evaluated against norms representing most major U.S. metropolitan areas, with sparser international representation (see Figure 1).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://ergreports.com/our-team/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ergreports.com/our-team/</guid>
      <description>eg was founded in 2022 by John Kulas (aka “John-o”), an Industrial and Organizational Psychologist. The foundation of the consultancy is on Statistical and Psychometric applications. The services provided are delivered within a systems-oriented framework of Organizational Development. The mission of eg includes a continuation of collaboration and mentorship for graduate students in Industrial and Organizational Psychology, and these students and former students contribute to eg’s services via structured contract assignments.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://ergreports.com/automation/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ergreports.com/automation/</guid>
      <description>Process automation 🚀We help organizations transition to -enabled automated work processes. Why ? Because it is:
Powerful
Flexible
FreeWe rely on  to drive all of our internal business functions. For example, we use the platform to scrape data from websites, automate reports, and consolidate data into centralized repositories. The system that we use is generalizable - your needs are of course unique but can also be automated via application of standard principles.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://ergreports.com/references/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ergreports.com/references/</guid>
      <description>Professional resources 📚:We maintain libraries of resources that have been created over the years either by eg personnel or graduate students in Industrial and Organizational Psychology that have had a former association with Dr. Kulas. These resources all share a goal of furthering the advancement of testing and assessment. A partial listing of these resources (as well as hyperlinks to the resources themselves) is presented below:
R Resources:Working with RMarkdown (García Prieto Palacios Roji &amp;amp; Kulas, 2020)Working with GitHub (García Prieto Palacios Roji et al.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://ergreports.com/testing/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ergreports.com/testing/</guid>
      <description>Assessments AuditingThe sheer volume of assessments that organizations can accumulate can be overwhelming. Over 30 years of experience in authoring, validating, and implementing assessments gives us a unique perspective regarding assessment utility.
An assessment audit evaluates the current cost and benefit of assessments used for purposes of selection, training, and employee experience. Returns on investment are calculated and the audited organization receives a comprehensive report regarding the relative cost and benefit of each individual assessment as well as the overall assessment strategy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>location</title>
      <link>https://ergreports.com/location/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ergreports.com/location/</guid>
      <description>We’d ❤️ to hear from you!{&#34;x&#34;:{&#34;url&#34;:&#34;index_files/figure-html//widgets/widget_unnamed-chunk-2.html&#34;,&#34;options&#34;:{&#34;xdomain&#34;:&#34;*&#34;,&#34;allowfullscreen&#34;:false,&#34;lazyload&#34;:false}},&#34;evals&#34;:[],&#34;jsHooks&#34;:[]}eg:945 Broadway St NE
Minneapolis, MN 55413
kulasj@montclair.edu
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://ergreports.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2016 21:48:51 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ergreports.com/about/</guid>
      <description>This is a &amp;ldquo;hello world&amp;rdquo; example website for the blogdown package. The theme was forked from @jrutheiser/hugo-lithium-theme and modified by Yihui Xie.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Engagement Survey Feedback Presentation Slides (Example/Tutorial)</title>
      <link>https://ergreports.com/slides/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ergreports.com/slides/</guid>
      <description>background-image: url(https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/b/be/Sharingan_triple.svg)
???
Image credit: Wikimedia Commons
class: inverse, center, middle
Get StartedHello WorldInstall the xaringan package from Github:
remotes::install_github(&amp;quot;yihui/xaringan&amp;quot;)–
You are recommended to use the RStudio IDE, but you do not have to.
Create a new R Markdown document from the menu File -&amp;gt; New File -&amp;gt; R Markdown -&amp;gt; From Template -&amp;gt; Ninja Presentation;1–</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
